<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reference on WebLogic Remote Console</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.8/reference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reference on WebLogic Remote Console</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.8/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Frequently asked questions</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.8/reference/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.8/reference/faqs/</guid>
      <description>This section provides answers to frequently asked questions about the WebLogic Remote Console.&#xA;Can I connect the WebLogic Remote Console to domains running in WebLogic on Oracle Cloud Infrastructure? Yes, you can. First, make sure that the domain&amp;rsquo;s administration server is publicly accessible so the WebLogic Remote Console can establish a connection to the administration server. Then, in the WebLogic Remote Console, enter your credentials and the publicly accessible URL for the WebLogic Administration Server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Known issues</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.8/reference/known_issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.8/reference/known_issues/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the limitations and known issues (and their workarounds if available) of the WebLogic Remote Console.&#xA;Limitations In the current release of WebLogic Remote Console, you cannot:&#xA;Record WLST scripts while you configure WebLogic Server using the WebLogic Remote Console. Test automatically if an application was successfully deployed. See Test Application Deployment for a manual option. Reorder security providers in WDT model file providers. However, you can download the WDT model file and edit the YAML file manually to rearrange the order of the security providers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot issues</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.8/reference/troubleshoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.8/reference/troubleshoot/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to prevent and recover from issues in the WebLogic Remote Console.&#xA;Basic troubleshooting steps Review Known issues to see if there is a workaround. Check the log files for errors. The WebLogic Remote Console provides log files for both front and back end processes. See Check Log Files to learn how to access these files. Update to the latest versions of the WebLogic Remote Console and the WebLogic Remote Console extension.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review security issues</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.8/reference/security-warnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.8/reference/security-warnings/</guid>
      <description>WebLogic Server regularly checks domains to ensure they comply with its recommended security policies. If a domain does not meet the recommendations, a security warning is logged and displayed in the WebLogic Remote Console.&#xA;You must have the July 2021 Patch Set Update (PSU) for WebLogic Server applied to your domain to receive security warnings.&#xA;When there are active security warnings in your domain, a banner with red text appears at the top of the WebLogic Remote Console window.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
