<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WebLogic Remote Console</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WebLogic Remote Console</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Build from source</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/develop/build-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/develop/build-source/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites Before you can build the WebLogic Remote Console, you need to install the following software in your local build environment:&#xA;Java SE 11 Maven 3.6.1+ nodejs 14.16+ This download includes npm. Oracle JET 14.1.0 client libraries To install the required Oracle JET software, run npm install --location=global @oracle/ojet-cli@~14.1.0. On Linux and macOS, you will need to use sudo. You can verify you&amp;rsquo;ve installed the correct versions of the listed software by running the following commands:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore the WebLogic Remote Console</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/setup/console/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/setup/console/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Remote Console offers an alternative option for administering WebLogic Server domains. It not only allows you to edit Administration Servers, but also build WebLogic Deploy Tooling (WDT) model files and property lists.&#xA;While the WebLogic Remote Console shares many features with the Administration Console, its functionality is slightly different. See Differences with the Administration Console for more information.&#xA;Basic layout The WebLogic Remote Console presents a simple user interface that varies slightly across different providers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently asked questions</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/reference/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/reference/faqs/</guid>
      <description>This section provides answers to frequently asked questions about the WebLogic Remote Console.&#xA;Can I connect the WebLogic Remote Console to domains running in WebLogic on Oracle Cloud Infrastructure? Yes, you can. First, make sure that the domain&amp;rsquo;s administration server is publicly accessible so the WebLogic Remote Console can establish a connection to the administration server. Then, in the WebLogic Remote Console, enter your credentials and the publicly accessible URL for the WebLogic Administration Server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/projects/</guid>
      <description>A project is a group of providers connections to WebLogic Administration Servers, WebLogic Deploy Tooling (WDT) models, WDT composite models, or property lists.&#xA;Create a project Open File &amp;gt; New Project.&#xA;Enter a name for the project and click OK. The new project will appear in the Kiosk. Next, you&amp;rsquo;ll add a provider to the project.&#xA;Expand the Kiosk and beside the project name, click ⋮. Select one of the following options to add provider:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contribute to WebLogic Remote Console</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/develop/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/develop/contribute/</guid>
      <description>We welcome contributions to this repository from anyone.&#xA;If you want to submit a pull request to fix a bug or enhance an existing feature, please first open an issue and link to that issue when you submit your pull request.&#xA;If you have any questions about a possible submission, feel free to open an issue too.&#xA;Contributing to the WebLogic Remote Console repository Pull requests can be made under The Oracle Contributor Agreement (OCA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Known issues</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/reference/known_issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/reference/known_issues/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the limitations and known issues (and their workarounds if available) of the WebLogic Remote Console.&#xA;Limitations In the current release of WebLogic Remote Console, you are unable to:&#xA;Record WLST scripts while you configure WebLogic Server using the WebLogic Remote Console. Minimum web browser viewport size Issue The font sizes in the WebLogic Remote Console are governed by the Oracle JET Redwood style. They are larger than the ones used in the WebLogic Server Administration Console, and the entry fields are a bit larger in height and width.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Editing security data</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/providers/administration-server/security-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/providers/administration-server/security-data/</guid>
      <description>You can manage security data and supported security providers for your domain in the Security Data tree perspective.&#xA;You must be logged in as a user with the Admin role and have the WebLogic Remote Console extension installed to access this perspective. See Install the WebLogic Remote Console for instructions.&#xA;Any changes you make within the Security Data perspective are immediate - you don&amp;rsquo;t need to commit or reboot the server to apply your changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate dashboards</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/dashboards/</guid>
      <description>Dashboards let you quickly assess the state of your WebLogic Server domain. With dashboards, you can assemble a set of criteria (or &amp;lsquo;filters&amp;rsquo;) and WebLogic Remote Console will match them against any bean in your domain and return the results. Because you control the filters of the dashboard, you control what you see and can determine the importance of the results, updating the dashboard as needed.&#xA;Dashboards are only available for Administration Server providers (in the Monitoring Tree perspective).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Property lists</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/providers/property-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/providers/property-list/</guid>
      <description>Property lists are an editable set of key-value pairs.&#xA;You can add property lists to WDT model files as WDT variables, which streamline the configuration of WDT model files. Once connected to a WDT model file, you can insert a property into the WDT model file as a WDT model token and edit token values from within the property list.&#xA;Create a new property list Expand the Kiosk and beside the project name, click ⋮.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customize connection settings</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/advanced-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/advanced-settings/</guid>
      <description>You can customize the default connection settings of the WebLogic Remote Console by modifying its Java system properties.&#xA;Edit Java system properties Java system properties Some possible customizations:&#xA;Connect to a WebLogic domain using SSL/TLS Specify a listen address for the WebLogic Remote Console host Configure a proxy server Change the network timeout settings for the server Disable host name verification in the connections to the WebLogic domain Set the SameSite cookie attribute if required for web browser support Connect to a WebLogic domain running on Kubernetes Specify an alternative location for the JDK Establish an insecure connection to an Administration Server Edit Java system properties You can create a file that modifies the WebLogic Remote Console according to your preferences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot issues</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/reference/troubleshoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/reference/troubleshoot/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to prevent and recover from issues in the WebLogic Remote Console.&#xA;Basic troubleshooting steps Review Known issues to see if there is a workaround. Check the log files for errors. The WebLogic Remote Console provides log files for both front and back end processes. See Check Log Files to learn how to access these files. Update to the latest versions of the WebLogic Remote Console and the WebLogic Remote Console extension.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use an alternative logging configuration file</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/develop/alternative-logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/develop/alternative-logging/</guid>
      <description>By default, the WebLogic Remote Console uses the logging.properties file inside the runnable/console-backend-server-{version}.jar file.&#xA;If the default configuration is sufficient, then you don&amp;rsquo;t need to do anything. However, if you want to tweak the logger configuration without regenerating the runnable/console-backend-server-{version}.jar file, you can pass the -Djava.util.logging.config.file=&amp;lt;path-to-logging.properties&amp;gt; Java system property when starting the console.&#xA;For example:&#xA;-Djava.util.logging.config.file=runnable/etc/logging.properties If there is a problem using the specified path, then the logging.properties inside the runnable/console-backend-server-{version}.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contribute to the documentation</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/develop/docs-contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/develop/docs-contribute/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Remote Console documentation is produced using the Hugo static site generator. The webpages are created in markdown and hosted within the same repository as the WebLogic Remote Console. This makes it easy to suggest edits and improvements directly to the documentation.&#xA;To make an update to the documentation:&#xA;Clone the repository.&#xA;$ git clone https://github.com/oracle/weblogic-remote-console Create a new branch.&#xA;$ git checkout -b &amp;lt;your-branch&amp;gt; Make your changes to the documentation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review security issues</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/reference/security-warnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/reference/security-warnings/</guid>
      <description>WebLogic Server regularly checks domains to ensure they comply with its recommended security policies. If a domain does not meet the recommendations, a security warning is logged and displayed in the WebLogic Remote Console.&#xA;You must have the July 2021 Patch Set Update (PSU) for WebLogic Server applied to your domain to receive security warnings.&#xA;When there are active security warnings in your domain, a banner with red text appears at the top of the WebLogic Remote Console window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade the WebLogic Remote Console</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Upgrade to the latest WebLogic Remote Console and take advantage of the latest features in both the console and WebLogic Server.&#xA;The WebLogic Remote Console extension is periodically updated. Check if there&amp;rsquo;s also a newer version of the extension available when you upgrade the WebLogic Remote Console.&#xA;Delete and replace any previous versions of the extension. Keeping multiple versions of the extension installed can lead to unexpected behavior.&#xA;If you use config.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WDT model files</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/providers/wdt-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/providers/wdt-model/</guid>
      <description>WDT metadata models are descriptions of a WebLogic Server domain configuration, generally written in YAML but occasionally JSON. These models are not connected to a live domain and you edit them &amp;lsquo;offline&amp;rsquo; before using the WebLogic Deploy Tooling (WDT) to build or modify live domains from the models.&#xA;See the WebLogic Deploy Tooling documentation for more information.&#xA;The WebLogic Remote Console assumes WDT model files are in YAML format. If you upload a file with no file extension, the WebLogic Remote Console will convert it to YAML format after you save your changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check log files</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/logging/</guid>
      <description>You can inspect log files to ensure that the WebLogic Remote Console is functioning correctly.&#xA;Front end To view the log file for issues related to the front end of the WebLogic Remote Console:&#xA;Desktop application Open View &amp;gt; Toggle Developer Tools and select the Console tab.&#xA;Browser application In the browser tab with WebLogic Remote Console, open the Developer Tools and select the Console tab.&#xA;Back end To view the log file for issues related to the back end of the WebLogic Remote Console:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differences with the Administration Console</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/setup/admin-console-diff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/setup/admin-console-diff/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Remote Console is distinct from the WebLogic Server Administration Console that is deployed as part of your WebLogic domain. As you explore the WebLogic Remote Console, you&amp;rsquo;ll notice key differences between the two consoles:&#xA;The user interface has been completely redesigned to conform to the Oracle Redwood theme included with Oracle JET. The configuration and monitoring runtime content is separated into separate pages in the Remote Console. In the WebLogic Server Administration Console, the configuration and runtime information is presented on one page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WDT composite models</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/providers/wdt-composite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/providers/wdt-composite/</guid>
      <description>WDT composite models are read-only representations of multiple, merged WDT model files.&#xA;Create a WDT composite model Create or upload two or more WDT model files to the WebLogic Remote Console.&#xA;Expand the Kiosk and beside the project name, click ⋮. Select Add WDT Composite Model File Provider.&#xA;Enter a name for the WDT Composite Model. This is the name that will appear in the Project list of providers so you can identify which provider you’re working on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand access discrepancies</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/role-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.5/userguide/role-access/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Remote Console restricts what non-administrator users can see or do. Users with the roles Deployer, Monitor, or Operator are only shown the areas and features necessary for their role. These restrictions range from broad (hiding the entire Edit Tree perspective from users in the Monitor role) to narrow (hiding Create buttons on some pages). For full access to all the functionality of the WebLogic Remote Console, log in as an administrator.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
