<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Provider types on WebLogic Remote Console</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.3.0/userguide/providers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Provider types on WebLogic Remote Console</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.3.0/userguide/providers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Administration Servers</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.3.0/userguide/providers/administration-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.3.0/userguide/providers/administration-server/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Remote Console can connect directly to a WebLogic Administration Server to view and edit its domain, much like the WebLogic Server Administration Console, though there are some differences.&#xA;You can save the connection details for multiple WebLogic Administration Servers, making it easy to switch between domains with a click.&#xA;Connect to a WebLogic Administration Server Start the WebLogic Administration Server. Expand the Kiosk and beside the project name, click ⋮.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Property lists</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.3.0/userguide/providers/property-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.3.0/userguide/providers/property-list/</guid>
      <description>Property lists are an editable set of key-value pairs.&#xA;You can add property lists to WDT model files as WDT variables, which streamline the configuration of WDT model files. Once connected to a WDT model file, you can insert a property into the WDT model file as a WDT model token and edit token values from within the property list.&#xA;We recommend that you use the desktop application over the browser application when working with property list files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WDT model files</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.3.0/userguide/providers/wdt-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.3.0/userguide/providers/wdt-model/</guid>
      <description>WDT metadata models are descriptions of a WebLogic Server domain configuration, generally written in YAML but occasionally JSON. These models are not connected to a live domain and you edit them &amp;lsquo;offline&amp;rsquo; before using the WebLogic Deploy Tooling (WDT) to build or modify live domains from the models.&#xA;See the WebLogic Deploy Tooling documentation for more information.&#xA;We recommend that you use the desktop application over the browser application when working with WDT model files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WDT composite models</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.3.0/userguide/providers/wdt-composite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.3.0/userguide/providers/wdt-composite/</guid>
      <description>WDT composite models are read-only representations of multiple, merged WDT model files.&#xA;Create a WDT composite model Create or upload two or more WDT model files to the WebLogic Remote Console.&#xA;Expand the Kiosk and beside the project name, click ⋮. Select Add WDT Composite Model File Provider.&#xA;Enter a name for the WDT Composite Model. This is the name that will appear in the Project list of providers so you can identify which provider you’re working on.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
