<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WebLogic Remote Console</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WebLogic Remote Console</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Build from source</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/develop/build-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/develop/build-source/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites Before you can build the WebLogic Remote Console, you need to install the following software in your local build environment:&#xA;Java SE 11 Maven 3.6.1+ nodejs 14.16+ This download includes npm. Oracle JET 10.1.0 client libraries To install the required Oracle JET software, run npm install -g @oracle/ojet-cli@~10.1.0. On Linux and macOS, you will need to use sudo. You can verify you&amp;rsquo;ve installed the correct versions of the listed software by running the following commands:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore the WebLogic Remote Console</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/setup/console/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/setup/console/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Remote Console provides a redesigned interface for WebLogic Server domain configuration. The new user interface applies the standards of the Oracle Redwood design system included with Oracle JET.&#xA;The WebLogic Remote Console user interface consists of the following sections:&#xA;Kiosk NavStrip Navigation Tree Content Pane Kiosk The Kiosk (located in the bottom right corner of the WebLogic Remote Console) is where you perform the administrative aspects of the WebLogic Remote Console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently asked questions</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/reference/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/reference/faqs/</guid>
      <description>This section provides answers to frequently asked questions about the WebLogic Remote Console.&#xA;Can I connect the WebLogic Remote Console to domains running in WebLogic on Oracle Cloud Infrastructure? Yes, you can. First, make sure that the domain&amp;rsquo;s administration server is publicly accessible so the WebLogic Remote Console can establish a connection to the administration server. Then, in the WebLogic Remote Console, enter your credentials and the publicly accessible URL for the WebLogic Administration Server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/userguide/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/userguide/projects/</guid>
      <description>A project is a group of connections to either WebLogic Administration Servers or WebLogic Deploy Tooling (WDT) models or both.&#xA;Create a project Open File &amp;gt; New Project. Enter a name for the project and click OK. The new project will appear in the Kiosk. Expand the Kiosk and beside the project name, click ⋮. Select either Add Admin Server Connection Provider or Add WDT Model File Provider. You can add multiple of either to the project and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter which order you add them in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contribute to WebLogic Remote Console</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/develop/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/develop/contribute/</guid>
      <description>We welcome contributions to this repository from anyone.&#xA;If you want to submit a pull request to fix a bug or enhance an existing feature, please first open an issue and link to that issue when you submit your pull request.&#xA;If you have any questions about a possible submission, feel free to open an issue too.&#xA;Contributing to the WebLogic Remote Console repository Pull requests can be made under The Oracle Contributor Agreement (OCA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edit domain configurations</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/userguide/edit-domain-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/userguide/edit-domain-config/</guid>
      <description>The domain configuration process in the WebLogic Remote Console is similar to the Administration Console. When you start editing the domain, a configuration lock is placed on the domain that blocks other users from making simultaneous changes. Once you&amp;rsquo;re are satisfied with your changes, you can &amp;lsquo;activate&amp;rsquo; these changes and perpetuate them to the administration and management servers.&#xA;Configuration locks do not apply to WDT model files. As WDT model files are not connected to live domains, they do not require any locks to prevent conflicting changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Known issues</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/reference/known_issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/reference/known_issues/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the known issues and workarounds, if available, as well as the limitations of the console in this release.&#xA;Limitations The following features are not available in this release of the WebLogic Remote Console:&#xA;Manage the security data from WebLogic Server security providers that is external to the WebLogic configuration, such as users, groups, roles, policies, credential maps, and so on. Record WLST scripts while you configure WebLogic Server using the WebLogic Remote Console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customize connection settings</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/userguide/advanced-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/userguide/advanced-settings/</guid>
      <description>You can customize the default connection settings of the WebLogic Remote Console by modifying its Java system properties.&#xA;Edit Java system properties in the desktop application Edit Java system properties in the browser-based application Java system properties Some possible customizations:&#xA;Connect to a WebLogic domain using SSL/TLS Specify a listen address for the WebLogic Remote Console host Change the network timeout settings for the server Disable host name verification in the connections to the WebLogic domain Set the SameSite cookie attribute if required for web browser support Connect to a WebLogic domain running on kubernetes Edit Java system properties in the desktop application If you installed the WebLogic Remote Console desktop application, you can edit a config.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot issues</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/reference/troubleshoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/reference/troubleshoot/</guid>
      <description>This page provides guidelines to help troubleshoot console issues.&#xA;Check log files for errors The WebLogic Remote Console provides log files for both front and back end processes. For instructions on how to access these log files, see Check Log Files.&#xA;Diagnose invalid WebLogic configuration issues Administration Server The WebLogic Remote Console catches most validation errors when you click Save, or when you commit the change using the shopping cart. If an error message displays, you need to identify and correct the problem that caused the error before you can activate the changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use an alternative logging configuration file</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/develop/alternative-logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/develop/alternative-logging/</guid>
      <description>By default, the WebLogic Remote Console uses the logging.properties file inside the runnable/console-backend-server-{version}.jar file.&#xA;If the default configuration is sufficient, then you don&amp;rsquo;t need to do anything. However, if you want to tweak the logger configuration without regenerating the runnable/console-backend-server-{version}.jar file, you can pass the -Djava.util.logging.config.file=&amp;lt;path-to-logging.properties&amp;gt; Java system property when starting the console.&#xA;For example:&#xA;-Djava.util.logging.config.file=runnable/etc/logging.properties If there is a problem using the specified path, then the logging.properties inside the runnable/console-backend-server-{version}.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contribute to the documentation</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/develop/docs-contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/develop/docs-contribute/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Remote Console documentation is produced using the Hugo static site generator. The webpages are created in markdown and hosted within the same repository as the WebLogic Remote Console. This makes it easy to suggest edits and improvements directly to the documentation.&#xA;To make an update to the documentation:&#xA;Clone the repository.&#xA;$ git clone https://github.com/oracle/weblogic-remote-console Create a new branch.&#xA;$ git checkout -b &amp;lt;your-branch&amp;gt; Make your changes to the documentation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade the WebLogic Remote Console</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/userguide/upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/userguide/upgrade/</guid>
      <description>We encourage you to stay up to date with the latest version of the WebLogic Remote Console since it is regularly updated to work with the latest versions of WebLogic Server, including patches.&#xA;Desktop application To check for newer versions of the desktop application, go to Help &amp;gt; Check For Updates. If a newer version is available, a dialog box will open where you can choose to go to the GitHub webpage for the latest WebLogic Remote Console release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check Log Files</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/userguide/logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/userguide/logging/</guid>
      <description>You can inspect log files to ensure that the WebLogic Remote Console is functioning correctly.&#xA;Front end To view the log file for issues related to the front end of the WebLogic Remote Console:&#xA;Desktop application Open View &amp;gt; Toggle Developer Tools and select the Console tab.&#xA;Browser application In the browser tab with WebLogic Remote Console, open the Developer Tools and select the Console tab.&#xA;Back end To view the log file for issues related to the back end of the WebLogic Remote Console:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differences With the Administration Console</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/setup/admin-console-diff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/setup/admin-console-diff/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Remote Console is distinct from the WebLogic Server Administration Console that is deployed as part of your WebLogic domain. As you explore the WebLogic Remote Console, you&amp;rsquo;ll notice key differences between the two consoles:&#xA;The user interface has been completely redesigned to conform to the Oracle Redwood theme included with Oracle JET. The configuration and monitoring runtime content is separated into separate pages in the Remote Console. In the WebLogic Server Administration Console, the configuration and runtime information is presented on one page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand access discrepancies</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/userguide/role-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.1.0/userguide/role-access/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Remote Console restricts what non-administrator users can see or do. Users with the roles Deployer, Monitor, or Operator are only shown the areas and features necessary for their role. These restrictions range from broad (hiding the entire Edit Tree perspective from users in the Monitor role) to narrow (hiding Create buttons on some pages). For full access to all the functionality of the WebLogic Remote Console, log in as an administrator.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
