<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Get started on WebLogic Remote Console</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.4/setup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Get started on WebLogic Remote Console</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.4/setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Explore the WebLogic Remote Console</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.4/setup/console/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.4/setup/console/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Remote Console offers an alternative option for administering WebLogic Server domains. It not only allows you to edit Administration Servers, but also build WebLogic Deploy Tooling (WDT) model files and property lists.
While the WebLogic Remote Console shares many features with the Administration Console, its functionality is slightly different. See Differences with the Administration Console  for more information.
Basic layout The WebLogic Remote Console presents a simple user interface that varies slightly across different providers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Differences with the Administration Console</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.4/setup/admin-console-diff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-remote-console/2.4.4/setup/admin-console-diff/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Remote Console is distinct from the WebLogic Server Administration Console that is deployed as part of your WebLogic domain. As you explore the WebLogic Remote Console, you&amp;rsquo;ll notice key differences between the two consoles:
 The user interface has been completely redesigned to conform to the Oracle Redwood theme included with Oracle JET. The configuration and monitoring runtime content is separated into separate pages in the Remote Console. In the WebLogic Server Administration Console, the configuration and runtime information is presented on one page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
